https://harmonscents.com/privacy-policy/

My Account
HAVE A QUESTION? NEED HELP?
Privacy Policy
We at HARMON SCENTS are committed to the responsible use of your personal information and the protection of your privacy. This privacy policy applies to all the products and services described on our web site.
We strongly encourage you to read this policy carefully. If you have any questions about our policy or our use of your personal information, please feel free to contact us by sending an email to harmonscents@duellshotoutdoors.com or by writing to us at:
HARMON SCENTS
400 Rusch Rd.
Traverse City, MI 49696
USA
Attn: Privacy Issues/Chief Executive Officer
We may update this policy from time to time to reflect changes in our use of your personal information and/or applicable law. Any changes made to our policy will be reflected in an updated policy (denoted by an effective date later than the one currently identified above) posted to our web site.
In order to provide our full range of services and provide the best customer experience for our customers, we may collect the following types of information:
Certain aspects of our web site allow you to submit personal information to us (such as your name, email address, telephone number and mailing address) via internet browser based forms or by sending us an e-mail. We also collect user provided information (both electronically and physically) at trade shows, exhibitions and similar events. We may retain those communications in order to process your request, respond to such communications or improve the quality of our customer experience. We require you to register with our web site and/or to submit a credit card for payment prior to the receipt of certain services on our web site, such as the purchase of a product from our online store. We take reasonable steps to encrypt your credit card information as it is processed and stored on our servers.
When you visit our web site, we may send one or more small files, commonly referred to as “cookies”, which allow us to uniquely identify your internet browser. We use these cookies to store information about you and to track your use of our web site, all in order to improve our customer experience. Your browser may enable you to delete or disable our cookie files. Deleting, disabling or restricting the receipt of our cookie files may affect your ability to access certain portions of our web site.
By accessing our web site, our internet servers automatically record information your internet browser sends when you visit a web site. These logs may contain information such as your internet protocol (IP) address, browser version, domain name, language, date and time, the referring web site and information in your cookie files. We may also present internet hyperlinks to other web sites in a format that enables us to track whether those links have been followed. We only use this information to improve the quality of the services we offer.
We will only use your personal information in order to (i) provide our services or information about our services to you, (ii) analysis in order to improve our services and operations, (iii) product development and (iv) for the specific reasons outlined out our web site when we collect your information.
If we use your information for a purpose different from those outlined above, we will ask for your consent prior to such use. You may choose to opt-out of such use at such time. You may also request we remove your personal information from our active systems at any time by contacting us at the email or street address noted above.
We will not share your personal information with third parties unless we have your consent or unless we have a good faith belief we are required to share such information to satisfy applicable law, including the prevention of fraud. We may share certain aggregated, non-personal information collected from you (such as your browser type) with third parties in order to improve our services, but such information will not be sufficient to individually identify you. If you wish to revoke your consent to our sharing of your personal information, you may contact us at the email or street address noted above to request we discontinue sharing your personal information.
If you make a purchase using our online store (but have not otherwise consented to our sharing your information with third parties), we automatically consider you to have chosen not to have your personal information shared for marketing purposes. You do not need to contact us to indicate this preference.
You may review and request changes to your personal information stored on our active systems by contacting us at the email or street address above.
We take reasonable measures to identify and prevent unauthorized access to our systems and disclosure of your personal information. We also restrict access to your personal information to only those persons who need to know the information in order to perform the services we offer. Your personal information may be stored on computers systems maintained by an agent or service provider of our company, each of which will be bound by agreement to protect the confidentiality of your personal information. Our computer systems are located in the United States of America, but the computer systems of our service providers may be located in another country. Your submission of personal information constitutes your consent to the transfer and storage of your information across international borders.
Our web site is not designed nor directed at anyone under the age of 18, and we do not knowingly accept personal information from persons under the age of 18. If we become aware a person under the age of 18 has provided us personal information, we will discontinue the use of such information and remove it from our active systems.
Privacy Policy
Return Policy
Shipping Policy
© 2020 Duell Shot Outdoors, LLC
Website Design and Development by Center Fire Creative
